

□ 428-275-1641 | Secodyscharfe@gmail.com | Acschar.github.io | Cochar | Cochar | Cochar.github.io | Cochar.github.io

About

Computer Science graduate currently working in Web, writing clean and maintainable code, helping build communication and efficiency within teams, and finding the simplest solution for the problem at hand.

My past & current employers have praised me for my strong work ethic and productive nature. I am self-directing, an autodidact, and can easily adapt to new situations.

- -Languages: Python, Javascript/Node, Ruby, Bash, Java/C#, (My|Postgre)SQL, Go, Elixir, HTML5/CSS
- -Software: Ansible, Docker, Vagrant, Gitlab, Jenkins, Nginx/Apache, Linux/OSX/Win, Jira, Webpack/Babel
- -Frameworks: Django, Rails, React/Redux/Apollo, Mithril.js, Ember, Selenium, React-Native, Phoenix
- -Skills: TDD, REST/GraphQL, Automation/Devops, Data-Structures/Algorithms, UX, Design-prototyping, Machine Learning (past experience)

I am interested in exploring the ways in which technology can construct human relations and ease the workload of daily life .

Asides from having a strong technical background in programming, I am also proficient in creating 3D Simulations, Models, as well as Sound Design in Ableton Live.

Experience _

Office National du Film - National Film Board of Canada

Montreal, Quebec

WEB DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

Dec 2014 - Apr 2017 •2 yrs 5 mos

- Participate in multiple team configurations working on: Transaction web service (Moneris/Django/Flask)
- Legacy system (500K LOC) refactoring and additions of REST endpoints and mobile specific functionality for customer facing mobile
- · Microservice construction and maintenance.
- Authentication (OpenID) / Authorization systems
- Mobile prototyping in iOS/Android (ReactNative)
- Dev & CI Environment maintenance (Gitlab/Jenkins/Ansible).
- · Participate in the Scrum environment: Sprint Planning, Dailies, Sprint Reviews, and Retro.
- Contract extended on review of performance

Framestore Montreal, Canada

ASSISTANT PIPELINE TD

Oct 2013 - Jul 2014 •10 mos

- · Prototype frontend and backend of web app to sync up incoming user data with already established company solutions. Technologies include Angular, Django, SQL.
- Gather requirements, develop, and test GUI plugins for Maya & Houdini VFX software used by animators & FX artists in a 230 person facility. Projects include hollywood films such as Edge of Tomorrow, Paddington, and Jupiter Ascending.
- Debug render process errors on 3000 core farm for multi-site workflows(Montreal & London).
- · Provide technical assistance to artists in how to use advanced technical features of company software
- Author python and bash scripts for network data migrations & file sanitization.

Self Employed Gallery Rye, Montreal

PHYSICAL INSTALLATION PROGRAMMER

Nov 2010 - Jan 2011 •3 mos

- · Co-produced multi-arts event at Gallery Rye, Montreal, Qc. Setup involved 3 bands, interactive technology & tactile experiences for 180 people, & licensed bar.
- Designed wall art-installation that permuted visual display based on user's commands from their web-devices to Uno-Board via Ap-
- Technologies included Arduino, Python, Google AppEngine, soldering.

VMC Game Labs

Montreal, Canada

QA TESTER *APr 2008 - Aug 2008 • 5 mos*

- Worked in a team finding a wide array of bug types in an up and coming EA Skate game.
- Immersed in tasks that included MS Excel, Video Editing, GIMP, and online bug-tracking database.
- Promoted to special-content testing group halfway through contract.

Education _

McGill University

Montreal, Canada

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.S), COMPUTER SCIENCE

2008-2013

• Activities & Societies Montreal Robotics Hackathon

CourseraMontreal, Canada

STANFORD MACHINE LEARNING COURSE BY ANDREW NG

2013-2013

• Andrew Ng's Famous Machine Learning course taught on the Coursera platform. Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, K-means Clustering, SVMs, Overfitting/Underfitting & other methods were taught.